

CONTACT ME AT

- 17/2053 KANDATHILPARAMBIL PERUMBADAPPU PALLURUTHY P O KOCHI 682006
- mesujithks3@gmail.com
- +91 9656008103
- https://mesujithks.github.io/
- in <u>@mesujithks</u>
- @mesujithks

KEY COMPETENCIES

- Industry experience building websites and web applications.
- Specialize in Java and have professional experience working with Spring Boot Framework (micro services) and Angular/React.
- Experience in working with Spring MVC, Hibernate, Spring Data JPA, TypeScript, jQuery, REST APIs and Oracle/MySql databases.
- Hands-on version control tool SVN, Git and code storage tool Github and Gitlab.
- Strong skills in planning and executing the functionality of the application.
- Ability to follow sprint/project plans and meet commitments
- Debug programs to resolve issues whenever reported or encountered by the QA team in the sprint delivery phase.

AWARDS RECEIVED

Rising Star Award (Most Valuable Fresher) - From Interland Technology Services 2020

SUJITH K S

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Fullstack Developer with demonstrated skills building high quality websites and mobile applications. I specialize in Spring Boot Micro Services and Angular / React and have professional experience working with Java and JavaScript. I also have experience working with Android Studio, & Flutter.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Techversant | November 2021 - present

- Develops systems and tools with emphasis on performance and scalability
- Maintains database schema as well as functional and technical documents

Software Developer

Interland Technology Services | July 2019 - October 2021

- Participated in all aspects of a project, from design and development to testing
- Worked on maintenance and enhancements for existing applications

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

B.Tech, Computer Science and Engineering

College of Engineering Cherthala | August 2015 - July 2019

- Affiliated to APJ Abdul Kalam Technological University
- CGPA: 7.51

Higher Secondary Education

SDPY HSS Palluruthy | June 2013 - March 2015

- KERALA STATE BOARD
- Marks: 96%